officialwire.com 2012-05-14

# OfficialWire: Privacy Policy

## Table Of Contents

  * The Information We Collect  

  * How We Use The Information  

  * Cookies & Web Beacons  

  * Collection Of Information By Third-Party Websites, Ad Servers, & Sponsors  

  * Our Commitment To Security  

  * How You Can Access Or Correct Information  

  * Special Note For Parents  

  * How To Contact Us  

  * Updates & Effective Date  

  * Revision Date  

## Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting OfficialWire. OfficialWire and all [OfficialWire Network](http://www.officialwire.com/static.php?action=terms#network) websites (Note: this link will take you to OfficialWire's main website) are owned by **Key Web Consulting LLC**.

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this statement explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this website. 

**The Information We Collect**  
On OfficialWire.com, you can order products, enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to one of our services such as our online newsletters, or participate in one of our online forums or communities. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, email address, telephone number, fax number and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services. Top

On OfficialWire you can submit information about other people. For example, you might submit a person's name and email address to send an electronic greeting card and, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you might submit the recipient's name and address. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages include: recipient's name, address, email address, and telephone number.

At certain parts of our website, only persons who provide us with the requested personally identifiable information will be able to order products, programs, and services or otherwise participate in the website's activities and offerings. Top

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our webpages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Firefox, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Microsoft Windows or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink, etc.). Top

**How We Use The Information**   
We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you. Top

We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when news or information has been posted or published on OfficialWire or to notify you when you have won one of our contests or when we make changes to our subscriber agreements, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter, or to contact you about your account with us. Top

We use the information that you provide about others to enable us to send them your gifts or cards. From time to time, we also may use this information to offer our products, programs, or services to them. The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs, or services. Top

If you choose to submit content for publication (e.g., articles, press releases, classified ads, letters to our editors, comments associated with articles and or a posting to a blog or a discussion board), we may publish your screen name and other information you have provided to us. Top

We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services. Top

We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request, or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of service, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Web Site and applicable laws or as otherwise required or permitted by law or consistent with legal requirements. In addition, we may transfer personally identifiable information about you if we, or one of our business units, are acquired by, sold to, or merged with another company. Agents and contractors who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Statement by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for us. Top

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Statement. Top

OfficialWire may disclose personally identifiable information to companies whose practices are not covered by this privacy statement (e.g., other marketers, magazine publishers, retailers, participatory databases, and non-profit organizations) that want to market products or services to you. If a site shares personally identifiable information, it will provide you with an opportunity to opt out or block such uses either at the point of submission of your personally identifiable information or prior to any such disclosure. Top

We may on occasion combine information we receive online with outside records to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you. If you have signed up to receive our emails and prefer not to receive marketing information from this website, follow the "unsubscribe" instructions provided on any marketing email you receive from this website. Top

Finally, the websites covered by this Privacy Statement will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses. Top

**Cookies & Web Beacons**   
To enhance your experience with our sites, many of our web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your email address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. However, once you choose to furnish The website with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. Top

We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services. Top

"Web beacons" or clear .gifs are small pieces of code placed on a web page to monitor the behavior and collect data about the visitors viewing a web page. For example, web beacons can be used to count the users who visit a web page or to deliver a cookie to the browser of a visitor viewing that page. We may use web beacons on this website from time to time for this and other purposes. Top

**Collection Of Information By Third-Party Websites, Ad Servers, & Sponsors**   
Some of our sites contain links to other websites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. Top

The website covered by this Privacy Statement sometimes may offer content (e.g., contests, sweepstakes, or promotions) that is sponsored by or co-branded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the website activity. We have no control over these third parties' use of this information. The website will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if these third parties will obtain such information. Top

**Our Commitment To Security**   
We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online. Top

**How You Can Access Or Correct Information**  
Access to personally identifiable information that is collected from our website may be accessible for a limited period of time from the point of collection. For example, if you created a password-protected account within our website, you can access that account to review the information you provided. Top

You may send an [email](http://www.officialwire.com/static.php?action=email_us) requesting access to or correction of your personally identifiable information. For verification purposes please include your first name, last name, email address and the password you use for said service. Top

**Special Note For Parents**   
The website you are visiting is one of our general audience sites. For more information about our online privacy practices for children's websites, consult the privacy notice at the children's website in which you are interested. Top

**How To Contact Us**   
If you have any questions or concerns about the online privacy statement for this website or its implementation you may contact us by [email](http://www.officialwire.com/static.php?action=email_us). Top

**Updates & Effective Date**   
From time to time, we may update this privacy statement. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information by placing a notice on our site. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it. Top

_Revised: February 6, 2011_ Top
